elitefitness.com 2018-10-22

# Privacy Policy - EliteFitness.com

Dear friends and fellow athletes,

At elitefitness.com, we have a strong commitment to your personal privacy. Your trust is so important to us that when you do business with Elite, you can be assured that your personal information will never be sold, given away, or mishandled. And, you can ask that your personal information be removed from our files at any time. Please take a look at our complete [Privacy Policy](https://www.elitefitness.com/privacy.html). 

Don't forget, EliteFitness.com has been online since 1996. That makes us older than Google! So remember, when you place an order at Elite Fitness, your VISA, Mastercard, AMEX, or Discover card number is encrypted, or scrambled, so completely, that it is unreadable during transit. You'll see a discreet charge from Elite Fitness on your billing statement. And you're 100% protected by our Safe Shopping Guarantee. |   
---|---  
  
Elite Fitness has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this site; Elite Fitness. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. 

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information and occassionally demographic information. We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. Most importantly, your email address is considered sacred. We don't sell or rent your digital mailbox. The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the delete/deactivate section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is only shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, etc.). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the delist/deactivate section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

Our online surveys asks visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and shared with other companies who may want to contact our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the delist/deactivate section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the delete/deactivate section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

We sometimes use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

## Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site contains links to other sites. Elite Fitness is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Delete/Deactivate

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can go to this [link where you can send us an email](http://support.elitefitness.com/support/).[](mailto:suggestions@elitefitness.com)
  2. You can send mail to the following postal address:  217 West 18th Street, PO BOX 1264, New York, NY 10113-1264 
  3. You can call the following telephone number: (888) 613-8959 

## Change/Modify

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. You can go to this [link where you can send us an email](http://support.elitefitness.com/support/).[](mailto:suggestions@elitefitness.com)
  2. You can send mail to the following postal address:  217 West 18th Street, PO BOX 1264, New York, NY 10113-1264 
  3. You can call the following telephone number: (888) 613-8959 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Elite Fitness  
217 West 18th Street  
#1264  
New York, NY 10113-1264 

Or, here's [a link where you can send us an email](http://support.elitefitness.com/support/). 

##### **elitefitness.com  
The Most Controversial Fitness Site On The Net!** **  
****  
****g spellwin@elitefitness.com  
(888) 613-8959**
